They're selling music but not selling out.
Empire Records is a music, comedy, drama film directed by Allan Moyle.
The employees of an independent music store learn about each other as they
try to stop the store from being absorbed by a large chain.
Corey Mason, played by Liv Tyler.
A.J., played by Johnny Whitworth.
Gina, played by Renée Zellweger.
Debra, played by Robin Tunney.
Joe Reaves, played by Anthony LaPaglia.
Lucas, played by Rory Cochrane.
Empire Records is a 1995 American coming-of-age comedy-drama film directed by Allan Moyle, written by Carol Heikkinen, and starring an ensemble cast including
Anthony LaPaglia, Maxwell Caulfield, Ethan Embry, Debi Mazar, Rory Cochrane, Johnny Whitworth, Robin Tunney, Renée Zellweger, and Liv Tyler.
The plot follows a group of record store employees
over the course of one exceptional day.
The employees try to stop the store from being sold to a large
chain, and learn about each other along the way.
Empire Records was theatrically released in the United
States on September 22, 1995, by Warner Bros.
to generally negative reviews and major box office losses.
It has since gone on to become a cult classic, with several
of its stars launching successful careers.
The film explores themes of pop star, older man younger woman
relationship, shoplifting, cupcake, twenty something.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.